(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],{e6Wu:function(e,a,l){"use strict";l.r(a),function(e){l("SYky"),l("hZTp");var a=l("y7Xl"),n=[a.a[0],a.a[13],a.a[18],a.a[21],a.a[2],a.a[31],a.a[14],a.a[35],a.a[22],a.a[4],a.a[16],a.a[30],a.a[26],a.a[5],a.a[32],a.a[20],a.a[8],a.a[17],a.a[19],a.a[10]],o=[a.a[3],a.a[9],a.a[19],a.a[14],a.a[28],a.a[35],a.a[5],a.a[24],a.a[15],a.a[17],a.a[12],a.a[18],a.a[31],a.a[29],a.a[6],a.a[0],a.a[26],a.a[22],a.a[13],a.a[7]],r=[a.a[3],a.a[11],a.a[23],a.a[25],a.a[27],a.a[33],a.a[34],a.a[2],a.a[15],a.a[17],a.a[12],a.a[18],a.a[31],a.a[29],a.a[6],a.a[9],a.a[26],a.a[22],a.a[13],a.a[1]],u=0,i=0,g=0,v=0,s=0,t=0,b=0,c=0,d=0,w=0,y=0,k=0,q=0,m=0,p=0,h=[n,o,r],E=function(a){var l=a.target.value.split(",");console.log(l),u+=parseInt(l[0]),i+=parseInt(l[1]),g+=parseInt(l[2]),v+=parseInt(l[3]),s+=parseInt(l[4]),t+=parseInt(l[5]),console.log(u),console.log(i),console.log(g),console.log(v),console.log(s),console.log(t),e(".progress-bar").css("width",(p+1)/20*100+"%").attr("aria-valuenow",p/20*100),19==p?M():(p++,I())},I=function(){document.getElementById("theWord").innerHTML=h[m][p].question,document.getElementById("ans1").innerHTML=h[m][p].answers[0].label,document.getElementById("ans2").innerHTML=h[m][p].answers[1].label,document.getElementById("ans3").innerHTML=h[m][p].answers[2].label,document.getElementById("ans1").value="".concat(h[m][p].answers[0].region1value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[0].region2value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[0].region3value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[0].region4value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[0].region5value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[0].region6value),document.getElementById("ans2").value="".concat(h[m][p].answers[1].region1value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[1].region2value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[1].region3value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[1].region4value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[1].region5value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[1].region6value),document.getElementById("ans3").value="".concat(h[m][p].answers[2].region1value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[2].region2value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[2].region3value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[2].region4value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[2].region5value,",").concat(h[m][p].answers[2].region6value)},M=function(){(b=u+i+g+v+v+t)>0?(c=Math.round(u/b*100),d=Math.round(i/b*100),w=Math.round(g/b*100),y=Math.round(v/b*100),k=Math.round(s/b*100),q=Math.round(t/b*100)):(c=0,d=0,w=0,y=0,k=0,q=0),document.getElementById("per1").innerHTML="".concat(c," %"),document.getElementById("per2").innerHTML="".concat(d," %"),document.getElementById("per3").innerHTML="".concat(w," %"),document.getElementById("per4").innerHTML="".concat(y," %"),document.getElementById("per5").innerHTML="".concat(k," %"),document.getElementById("per6").innerHTML="".concat(q," %"),e("#survey").addClass("hide"),e("#result").removeClass("hide"),console.log(c),console.log(d),console.log(w),console.log(y),console.log(k),console.log(q)},L=function(){m=Math.floor(3*Math.random()),e("#starter").addClass("hide"),I(),e("#psbar").removeClass("hide"),e("#survey").removeClass("hide")};e(document).ready((function(){document.querySelector("#info").addEventListener("click",f),document.querySelector("#startbtn").addEventListener("click",L),document.querySelector("#ans1").addEventListener("click",E),document.querySelector("#ans2").addEventListener("click",E),document.querySelector("#ans3").addEventListener("click",E),document.querySelector("#ans4").addEventListener("click",E)}));var f=function(){e("#infoModal").modal({show:!0})}}.call(this,l("EVdn"))},hZTp:function(e,a,l){},y7Xl:function(e,a,l){"use strict";l.d(a,"a",(function(){return n}));var n=[{key:1,question:"ییزي",answers:[{label:"يكفي",region1value:"10",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"9"},{label:"يشرب",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"نوع من أنواع الأحذية وأنتم بكرامة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:2,question:"جغمة",answers:[{label:"حفرة عميقة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"رشفة",region1value:"10",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"9",region6value:"5"},{label:"ثقيلة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:3,question:"هاليودعه",answers:[{label:"من أجل ذلك",region1value:"10",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"لننتظر قليلًا",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"دعنا لنودعه",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:4,question:"یتمقل",answers:[{label:"يعبس في وجهك",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"يغش ",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"يمعن النظر",region1value:"10",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"9",region6value:"5"}]},{key:5,question:"شفايه",answers:[{label:"فضول",region1value:"10",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"2"},{label:"سفره",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"منظر جميل",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:6,question:"جماھو",answers:[{label:"رفض شديد اللهجة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"مضحك ",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"أليس كذلك",region1value:"10",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:7,question:"فرقزت",answers:[{label:"قمت مذعورا",region1value:"0",region2value:"10",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"ركضت سريعًا",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"تجهزت للعمل",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:8,question:"مید من",answers:[{label:"أين تذهب؟",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"أين صنع؟",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"من تقصد؟",region1value:"0",region2value:"10",region3value:"4",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:9,question:"منقعر",answers:[{label:"منسدح على ظهره",region1value:"1",region2value:"10",region3value:"0",region4value:"3",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"مائل أو غير مستوي",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"مسطح الشكل",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:10,question:"ارقه",answers:[{label:"صحيح بلا شك",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"هذا هو",region1value:"3",region2value:"10",region3value:"2",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"يكفي هذا القدر",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:11,question:"ھب لي",answers:[{label:"أعطني",region1value:"0",region2value:"10",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"خذ مني",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"اذهب عني",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:12,question:"حندرفیني",answers:[{label:"اسم جني في عسير",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"نظر إلي بغضب",region1value:"0",region2value:"10",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"ضربني في كتفي",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:13,question:"خاشوقة",answers:[{label:"ثلاجة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"إبرة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"ملعقة",region1value:"0",region2value:"3",region3value:"10",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:14,question:"عرموط",answers:[{label:"كمثرى",region1value:"1",region2value:"0",region3value:"10",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"برتقال",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"بطيخ",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:15,question:"باصج",answers:[{label:"عنيد",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"قليل الملح",region1value:"3",region2value:"1",region3value:"10",region4value:"0",region5value:"2",region6value:"0"},{label:"جميل الرائحة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:16,question:"صمندیقة",answers:[{label:"الشخص الغني",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"الشخص المتباهي",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"الشخص الغبي",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"10",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:17,question:"غرشة",answers:[{label:"علبة",region1value:"0",region2value:"2",region3value:"10",region4value:"1",region5value:"3",region6value:"0"},{label:"مغرفة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"سكينة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:18,question:"غلج",answers:[{label:"قاسي",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"ثقيل",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"صعب",region1value:"2",region2value:"1",region3value:"10",region4value:"2",region5value:"1",region6value:"0"}]},{key:19,question:"یمصع",answers:[{label:"يطلب",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"يجر",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"10",region5value:"10",region6value:"8"},{label:"يهرب",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:20,question:"مخمج",answers:[{label:"متعفن",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"10",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"معلب",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"وسخ",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:21,question:"بكرج",answers:[{label:"صحن",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"كأس",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"برادة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"10",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:22,question:"یتمردغ",answers:[{label:"يلعب",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"يتبهذل",region1value:"4",region2value:"2",region3value:"3",region4value:"10",region5value:"10",region6value:"7"},{label:"يحمل",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:23,question:"ستیتة",answers:[{label:"الأخت الكبرى",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"10",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"أم الزوجة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"الجدة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:24,question:"الدقیسي",answers:[{label:"دورة المياه",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"مجلس الضيوف",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"غرفة تحت الدرج",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"10",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:25,question:"تھقى",answers:[{label:"تظن",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"8"},{label:"تحتسي القهوى",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"ترمي",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:26,question:"فاردز",answers:[{label:"شارك",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"ارحل",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"7"},{label:"اقترب",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:27,question:"مصع",answers:[{label:"بالغ بالأمر",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"يشد بقوة",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"6"},{label:"هدد بالموضوع",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:28,question:"ھماه",answers:[{label:"أليس كذلك؟",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"3"},{label:"جلب لي الهم والنكد",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"ملك له",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:29,question:"احترين",answers:[{label:"انتظريني",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"3"},{label:"شارع في حي الخبوب",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"يكاد يحترق من الحرارة ",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:30,question:"أزمل",answers:[{label:"أخشى عواقب أمر ما",region1value:"2",region2value:"1",region3value:"3",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"8"},{label:"أستعد للقدوم",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"أكثر جمالًا",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:31,question:"زاھب",answers:[{label:"راكب",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"جالس",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"جاهز",region1value:"6",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"10"}]},{key:32,question:"صایل",answers:[{label:"ولهان لشدة الشوق",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"غاضب",region1value:"2",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"9",region6value:"10"},{label:"يدمع من الفرح",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:33,question:"عذروب",answers:[{label:"عيب",region1value:"6",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"10"},{label:"من أسماء الخيل",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"عذر",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]},{key:34,question:"ھجت به",answers:[{label:"كتبت فيه أبياتًا من الشعر",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"ساعدته",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"ضاعت علومه",region1value:"3",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"10"}]},{key:35,question:"ذروق",answers:[{label:"كريم",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"بخيل",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"جبان",region1value:"4",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"10"}]},{key:36,question:"احلت",answers:[{label:"انهض",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"},{label:"ارم",region1value:"5",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"10",region6value:"10"},{label:"خذ",region1value:"0",region2value:"0",region3value:"0",region4value:"0",region5value:"0",region6value:"0"}]}]}},[["e6Wu",1,2]]]);